1. [About Noixion](https://noixion.tv/about/info)
2. Privacy

* * *

* * *

* * *

* * *

* * *

Privacy
-------

* * *

### Personal Information

You can visit Noixion websites without providing any personal data. In that case, we will only collect anonymous statistical data of general use (number of visitors, amount of data traffic, etc). Any additional voluntary information will be used only for the purpose for which you provided it, in order to give you the information or services you may require.

* * *

We will not disclose or sell your personal Information to anyone. Unless we need a third party to provide you with the information or services you require.

* * *

### Use of Cookies

During any visit to our site, the pages you see, along with a short text file called a ‘cookie’, are downloaded to your computer. Many websites do this, because cookies facilitate useful features such as the ability to identify whether a user has successfully logged into the site or to find out whether the computer (and probably its user) has visited the website before. Cookies may also allow to collect user aggregated behaviour, evaluate use and compile statistical reports.

* * *

You can set your browser to accept or reject cookies. These settings will typically be found in the ‘options’ or ‘preferences’ menu of your browser.

* * *

### Your rights

At any time, you have the right to:

* Access, rectification and deletion
* Opting-out at any time
* Applying restrictions
* Retraction of your consent to the processing
* Data portability
* Being informed of our data processing system

You have the right to raise a complaint to the corresponding supervisory authority (in Spain, AEPD). Before doing so, we kindly ask you to contact us and seek a friendly solution.

* * *

### How do we protect your data

We have implemented an advanced security system that protects your personal data against any accidental or unauthorised destruction, loss, alteration and access, or any other unauthorised process. Nevertheless, no system can guarantee 100% of security. Therefore, we strongly request you to choose a robust password and keep it confidential.

* * *

### Revisions

We may modify this Privacy Policy eventually. In that case we would modify this statement and send a notification by email (if any was provided).

### Forgot password?

Input your email to send you an email in order to restore your password.

* * *

Send reset instructions

### Restore your password

Choose a new password for your account

* * *

Restore password

* * *

OK

### Change the language

¿Do you want to change the language?

* * *

Spanish English

* * *

Decentralized Media Platform Powered By TRON (TRX)
==================================================

* * *

* Noixion TV is an advanced multimedia platform with decentralized storage and decentralized content delivery network (CDN) powered by TRON (TRX).
    
* This is a demo version working in a TRON testnet. To configure it with Tronlink please use https://noixion.tv:8443

* Content creators, storage users and end-users can earn TRX and NXN with Noixion TV. As a creator you can monetize your content under pay-per-view or ad-based models.
    
* 2 NXN in TRON testnet will be migrated to 1 NXN in the TRON main network.
    
* Sign up and visit your profile to get your affiliate link: the more users you invite to the platform, the more TRX and NXN you will earn in Noixion TV!

* * *

​

* * *

​

Noixion TV is powered by  
(TRC20 token in )

* * *

​

* * *

​

* * *

Everybody earns with Noixion!
-----------------------------

All users can earn cryptocurrencies (TRON and NXN) from the very moment they begin using Noixion: content creators, storage network owners… but also the end-users who view the content.

Noixion TV can be seen as a decentralized alternative to YouTube that uses Blockchain technologies and cryptocurrencies. Besides, ALL users can earn money easily on Noixion’s transparent platform.

Decentralized Storage and Contend Delivery Network
--------------------------------------------------

NOIXION users are free to choose between a centralized or a DECENTRALIZED storage system. You can also choose using your own servers (and monetize for their use) or third-party ones.

Noixion storage servers or nodes become part of a decentralized content distribution network (CDN), so that media content is cached on different servers. In each case, the server that is closest to the end user is selected, thus increasing the efficiency and quality of the platform.

There are different storage alternatives that users can choose from:

Smart Contracts compatibles with TRX and NXN are used to execute transactions on the platform, offering total traceability and transparency to the users.

* Kademlia (own implementation by Noixion)
    
* Bittorrent File System (BTFS)
    
* InterPlanetary File System (IPFS)
    
* Amazon S3
    
* Google Cloud Storage

TRON Network Smart Contracts and TRX
------------------------------------

Smart Contracts compatibles with TRX and NXN are used to execute transactions on the platform, offering total traceability and transparency to the users.

There are also 2 additional contracts: a dividends contract (as in Wink) and a specific contract for the storage networks.

Other features & advantages
---------------------------

Noixion TV implements its own affiliate system: if you recommend Noixion to other users (by sharing your referral link) you will earn a percentage of their earnings. This way you can earn TRX or NXN for free!

As an alternative to YouTube, Noixion TV allows to broadcast content without censorship and it is not affected by the recent problems of video monetization caused by the COPPA law.

Noixion TV is already a decentralized alternative to Twitch (streaming) too. Very soon we will also be a real alternative to Netflix or TikToK.

Why did we create Noixion TV?
-----------------------------

Do you know Justin Sun? Well, we share his vision: we “just” seek the decentralization of the Internet, fairer profit sharing and monetization, and less control (and yes, less censorship) by the “usual suspects”. And that’s why we use the TRON network.

Another of our main objectives is to bring user experience to the next level, making it simple and fast for Blockchain experts and novices alike. We believe that building a universal user experience is the key to bringing cryptocurrencies and TRX to mass adoption among the general public. #MassAdoption!!!

​

### Login

 Remember password

* * *

Login now

* * *

### Sign Up

By registering you accept and agree [Terms of Service](https://noixion.tv/about/terms) and [Privacy Policy](https://noixion.tv/about/privacy).

Sign up now

© [Noixion](https://noixion.tv/about/info) | [What is Noixion TV?](https://noixion.tv/what-is-noixion-tv) | [Terms of use](https://noixion.tv/about/terms) | [Privacy](https://noixion.tv/about/privacy) | [Twitter](https://twitter.com/NoixionNXN) | [Telegram](https://t.me/Noixion) | [Medium](https://medium.com/noixion)
